welcome to policy plus today we are
going to see best health insurance
policy
2025 before we going to video I request
to all if you want health insurance
please call 934
936 in
WhatsApp in this video we are comparing
Superstar plan from Star health
insurance and a Galaxy promise
Ultimate Care from Care Health Insurance
HDFC Ergo Optima secure NAA aspar
titanium
variant Tata Medicare Premier
plan manipal signal SVA utam variant IC
Lumbard
Elevate first we will check eligibility
age
nowadays most of the plants provide uh
entry age up to any age some plants only
like n manipal and Tata they provide up
to 65 years
only now we will compare available suers
range Superstar plan and IC Lumbard
provide unlimited coverage other plant
mostly they provide 2 CR or up to 3 CR
also now we will compare room R
limit most of the plant provide any room
uh in built or with
rider before continue this video I
request to all if you not sub subcribe
this Channel Please Subscribe this
channel also click this Bell button for
future
update now we will check pre and post
Hospital most of the plant provide up to
180 days post hospitalization
coverage now we will check no claim
bonus
here also some plans Superstar plan
Ultimate Care and ICC Lumbard provide
unlimited bonus other plans provide uh
100% or 10 times like
this now we will check restore
benefit almost all plants provide
Unlimited mited restore benefit ICC
lambar also provide
unlimited restore but 45 days for a
previous uh injury or illness
complications share accommodation if you
stay in the share accommodation what
will benefit you will
get majority of the plan provide a
premium discount
only when you choose share accommodation
you will get premium discount but if you
go higher room you have to pay
proportional
deductions HDFC Ergo data Medicare
provide uh some percentage of amount
like per day uh HDFC provide 800 tataa
provide maximum up to
2,000 pre-existing illas waiting
period Superstar plan provide 3 years
waiting F but quick Shield available
for diabetic hypertension ASA
cholesterol from day one
cover Galaxy also uh 3 years waiting
period but quick Shield available
for asthma blood pressure and
cholesterol Ultimate Care also available
right for reducing waiting period and a
day one coverage also
available n also day one coverage
available for diabetic and hypertension
T Medicare day one coverage available of
HMA pressure sugar
cholesterol even manipal also day one
coverage available ICC Lumbard also day
one coverage
available specific dises waiting period
like kitney store hernia joint
replacement ENT cact piles ulcer like
this waiting
period almost all plans waiting prod is
2 years some plans like Ultimate Care
and a Galaxy promise provide reducing
option now we will compare maternity
benefit
Superstar plan 2 years waiting period
delivery for 50,000 and 1 lakh available
Ultimate Care
also some percentage of Summer should
cover for maternity Neo 1 percentage of
Summer should has maternity benefit and
9 month waiting period moneyall signal 3
years waiting period maximum up to 5 LS
cover Galaxy promise also uh 10% of
Summer should maximum up to 5 lak
uh 2 years waiting period HDFC Ergo not
provide maternity cover T Medicare
provide maternity cover but 48 month
waiting period ICC Lampard provide one
year or 2 years waiting period maximum
up to 1 lakh delivery
coverage partic surgery
coverage here some plants only provide
periodic
surgery uh
Galaxy tataa Medicare ICC Lumbard
provide this
coverage CRA
limit almost all plants not have any
conditions for
cataract letal checkup benefit
all plant provide in build or Rider uh
as a health checkup
coverage ambulance
coverage almost all plans provide actual
amount Tata Medicare provide 5,000 to
maximum up to 30,000 based up on suers
air ambulance
coverage Superstar plan and HDFC tataa
provide up to 5 laks coverage Galaxy
promo provide 10% of sumers other plans
Ultimate Car n money and IC provide
coverage up to suur
I treatment
coverage all plants provide coverage up
to sumers
sh organ donor expenses
coverage all plants provide coverage up
to sumers sh manipal provide pre and
post hospitalization coverage also
Advanced treatment like chemotherapy
robotic surgery
coverage all plants provide coverage up
to sumers
sh domicillary
hospitalization patient Health not good
to take him to hospital or Hospital not
have bed in this condition uh we can can
take treatment at home that is called
promary
hospitalization all plants provide
coverage up to sumers
sh Home Care treatment some treatment we
can take from home
also here Galaxy promise provide up to
10% are maximum up to 5 lakhs
coverage tataa provide coverage only for
75 lakhs and above sumers sh only ICC
provate nursing at home
Rider n up to suers other plans Ultimate
Care and moneyall no
coverage coverage for non-medical items
like gloves mask sanitizer coverage this
is very very important uh if you not
take this cover uh you have to pay 20%
uh during hospitalization
surgery almost all plants provide this
coverage AA in built or
Rider premium lock Futures premium lock
means if you enter AG is 35 even if you
not claim you have to pay same uh
premium at Edge 45 or 60
also Superstar plan
provide premium lock up to 55
H Galaxy also provide up to 55 HED n
provide up to entry HED there is no
limit other options uh Ultimate Care
also provide premium free is
option extra
benefit Superstar wellness program 20%
discount available future sealed for uh
future husband or wife coverage without
or reduced waiting period Limitless care
one time we can claim any amount option
commerate visit uh if you treatment
taken in outside of your hometown travel
expansions possible to cover one person
from family premium waiver if insured
person died due to ask accident or
critical illness means next year premium
no need to pay a durable medical
equipment coverage available as a
rider Galaxy promise provide for ASO
coverage and reputation moral remains a
sleep disorder coverage and accidental
cover Hospital cash deductable option
for reduce the premium and emergency
domestic medical evacuation up to
10,000 ultimate C provide health
services and a loyalty boost Med
vouchers premium payback ultimate care
cover pass we can cover pass for one
month like this if you go to like this
and the C period also you will get
coverage and tenor
multiplayer and OPD reward Child
Protection spouse care that means Future
Care deductable option plus benefit that
means extra coverage wellness program
and woman care woman care means woman
out patient uh treatment and mental
health durable equipment coverage travel
plus uh that means travel uh coverage
Cancer Care and out
patient hdf go provide dental treatment
and accurated deductable option also
available NBA wellness program discount
30% and fast forward option for uh you
will get 3 years benefit in one year
Future Ready option and uh borderless
that means worldwide coverage cash back
that means discount uh deductable option
tataa Medicare provide prolong hospital
if you stay 10 days more than 10 days
hospitalization you will get 1% of su
Asia benefit and diagnosis coverage OPD
coverage OPD dental coverage acdal death
coverage cancer cover woman Shaka pocket
sa means that also out pression and a
deductible option and accidental sha
extra summer for
accident moneyall Ser also provide
personal accident and surplus benefit
means extra summer should H the rider
that means unlimited coverage for cancer
or stroke and major organ
transplantation and deductable
options IC Lumbard provate infinite care
that means one time you can claim any
amount and confidence benefit if you
stay 10 days hospitalizing claim up to
20,000 de accommodation relief compon
set visit durable medical equipment
coverage personal accident critical
illness Rider co- payment and a network
advantage B worldwide coverage
available even NRA discount also
available now we will compare premium
for 10 lakh family now we will compare
premium uh 35e husband and wife and two
child rest of India zones
this is the premium you can compare with
a benefit
also this all premium include of
GST please share suggestion and feedback
in comment section if you like this
video please subscribe this Channel and
share to your friends for health
insurance call 934
936 on WhatsApp see you in next
Insurance video thank you